So, longer portions of the interview with the most recent Hamas hostage have now come out.
What I'm about to show you is two more portions of that video.
The beginning portion will come from the Washington Post, and I want you to pay attention to how they have framed the information and where they stop in sharing.
The next portion of the interview is going to come from Al Jazeera, and these are concurrent parts of the interview.
And the reason why it's important to watch this is not because we're trying to frame Hamas as really nice folks.
That's not the point.
The point is that we must keep our ears and eyes and hearts open to the ways in which media and those in controlling of media are trying to control our ears, eyes, hearts, and minds from making decisions that really are going to affect all of us as a people because they don't care about us as a people.
My mom is telling the horrific stories.
She's saying that many, many people, a swarm of people came through the fence.
The fence cost two and a half billion shekels, and it didn't help even a little bit.
My mom is saying that she was taken on the back of a motorbike with her legs on one side and her head on another side.
That she was taken on one side and a man behind her, and that while she was being taken, she was hit by sticks by Shabab people.
Until they reached the tunnels.
There they walked for a few kilometers on the wet ground.
There are a huge, huge network of tunnels underneath.
It looks like a spiderweb.
Let's see.
My mom is talking about coming there.
When they arrived, they arrived into a large hall in which about 25 hostages were gathered.
And after two or three hours, those hostages, five of them, she among them, were taken into a separate room.
My mom is saying that they were very friendly towards them, and that they took care of them, that they were given the medicine.
They were given medicine, and they were treated.
One of the men with them had badly injured from a motorbike accident on the way, and the paramedic was looking after his wounds.
It was given medicine, and antibiotics, that the people were friendly, that they kept the place very clean.
My mom is talking about the conditions and being...
My mom is speaking about the time there.
She's telling us about sharing food with the people, that the people, when she first arrived, they told them that they are Muslims, and they're not going to hurt them.
And that they shared, they ate the same food that the Hamas was eating.
He's asking, why did you shake the hand of the Hamas terrorist in the visual?
They were gentle with us, our needs were supplied.
My mom is saying that they treat them kindly and provided for them.
I'm going to say that they didn't make any food with the help of the people.
My mom is saying that they didn't want to help bring their kids.
My mom asked me to tell this.
My mom is saying that I was getting sick.
My mom checked.
I'm getting sick because of my mom's love.
My mom's getting sick.
I'm gonna die.
My mom checked out.
My mom checked out the toilet.
I didn't know my mom checked out the toilet.